<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="fill_parent"
    android:layout_height="fill_parent">
    <CheckBox
        android:id="@+id/checkBoxConfirm"
        android:text="Are you sure?"
        android:textSize="@dimen/TextSizeMedium"
        android:textColor="@color/TextViewTextColor"
        android:textStyle="bold"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
        android:layout_marginLeft="20dp"
        android:layout_marginRight="20dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="10dp" />
    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:scrollbars="none"
        android:fillViewport="false"
        android:layout_above="@id/checkBoxConfirm"
        android:background="@color/white">
        <LinearLayout
            android:orientation="vertical"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:background="@color/white"
            android:padding="20dp">
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/txtTitle"
                android:text="SunMobile"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textSize="@dimen/TextSizeLarge"
                android:textColor="@color/TextViewTextColor"
                android:textStyle="bold" />
            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/txtMessage"
                android:text="This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  This is the message.  "
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textSize="@dimen/TextSizeMedium"
                android:textColor="@color/TextViewTextColor"
                android:paddingTop="10dp" />
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
</RelativeLayout>